5th, 2022, and we will have the
Education Minister, the First Christian Church.
Thank you very much.
Falling out, we love you.
We're grateful for this opportunity to come together as the people of
Miami.
I've got to pray for wisdom for insights and unity as we move forward and make our
community better.
In your words, you tell us to pray for the betterment of our communities and that's what we do right now.
We just lift up this group.
We just again ask for wisdom.
We ask for solid leadership and we just pray that my
Emma will continue to be a better place.
We love you.
Make us more like Jesus.
It says, name we pray.
Amen.
I'd like to leave you to the flag of the United States of America and do the
Republic for which they stand, the foundation of our God, and the
Individual, with liberty and justice for our God.
Thank you.
Before public input, I'm going to do personal appearances.
Five consent agenda staff recommends we approve out of six and seven.
Motion to approve.
Second.
All right.
Number eight.
The word of six month contract, amendments for concrete material,
C22-39, concrete sand, C22-40 and aggregate rock, C22-38.
And do you know anything about it?
Yeah, I'll take it.
So we buy for surplus, I'd like to have.
Well, I know our shape project, so we call it comm upgrade, or like, you know, we stock
stock from the streets and also water.
Right.
So yeah, that's what it's for.
I'll make a little show to the crew.
Second.
This is for professional services with our legal team and this first meeting occurred from October 1st, the October 31st of the entire month of October.
In during October we had several teleconference meetings with our team where we were basically a preparation regarding the GRA technical conference.
We've been reviewing the hydraulic modeling that's been going on in the sedimentation reports and in the preliminary report regarding the contaminated sediments in Tark Creek.
And again, this was all in preparation for the attendance of the technical conference took place October 12th and 13th to review GRA's updated study report.
And so with that, I'm simply asking that the council approve this and I'm preparing for the contract.
So, both the question I have the way this reads, this is not just for two days of work, right?
Oh, correct.
I just want to make sure that was clear.
Yes.
Very good catch.
Yeah.
Pretty much the entire month.
There was just all of the work that we were doing prior to and even the review of GRAP after was kind of regarding that one technical conference.
Which was a two-day conference, which everyone did at 10.
But then all was wondering where I came to RAPA.
Okay.
Yeah.
I mean, I saw I said October 1st October 31st, but then down at the bottom it says the 12th and 13th.
So that was just one clarity for those who might ask.
Good catch.
You think so.
Absolutely.
They did an amazing job.
And do we have budget money for this?
We do.
Yep.
It's well.
Okay.
But is there enough for their whole year?
Right.
I mean, we've been seeing two and three.
It's positive.
What's coming down the pipe?
Based on the previous year, we did budget enough for anticipating that where we're at in the relationship process.
I'm looking for this budget.
So turning things from in here.
750,000.
Where are we at currently?
How much do we spend?
We don't have to look at the actual whisper.
We're not very far into that at all.
Yeah.
We can't be that far into it.
I was going to say if we were 100, I'd be surprised.
Just based on what we've seen.
I'm going to say that.
We're at least 30%.
So what about for so this is for October, right?
Yeah.
What's your anticipation for November?
Would we have a couple more large ones coming because this one is for the preliminary.
prior to that. And then we had to have been working with the team through November, preparing the response to the technical.
So we had to file that briefing last week, which was file and that's what the emails you all been getting was our briefed as file, as well as the others that have filed for file 1, the organization file 1,
and we talked about that. Molly was going to scan those. She's been working on scanning those because she was getting in my card copy.
And then she was going to disseminate those. She's been working on that today.
So we got to met two, four, five today.
Oh, I'm going to say I think we've gotten this afternoon.
It's a series of PDF, it's a PDF of the series of information.
I'll make a motion to approve.
Second.
No.
Go inside.
Subner.
You stay.
All right.
Perfect.
10.
Other new business committee, which is a residence in the posting of this agenda.
11.
Trustee community announcements.
Proving 13 are going to be removed.
Is that correct?
That is correct.
At the time, we have given the agenda.
It was an anticipation that I would need an executive session.
I'm still ready to see her back.
I'm a particular, a particular property owner that I have not been back from yet.
So I haven't been for an energy body tonight.
Actually, 14 also.
It's a 12 13, 14 will be removed.
So I've arranged to 15 adjournment.
Second.